LOOUIS LOW



ABOUT ME

I have worked in the low level/embedded domain for ten years. I am suffered at the hands of C/C++ for several years before I discovered Python, and it felt like a breath of fresh air. I am now sharing my love.

I worked with several startups as a freelance or in-house developer. I build web services and apps using open source technologies.

CONTACT ME

PHONE NO (+6) 016 4910 454

EMAIL

loouis@gmail.com

ADDRESS

(confidential)

WEBSITE

https://loouislow81.github.io

SOCIAL

facebook.com/loouislow twitter.com/loouislow github.com/loouislow81



EXPERIENCE

dogsbark Software Engin

Software Engineer (architect) Canada

Embedded Design, Firmware Design, Prototyping and Automation. Machine Learning and Sound effect middle-ware

engineering.

Goody Software Engineer (frontend)

Malaysia

2016-2017, 2018-2019 Craft UI Material Design & System from scratch.

Pure CSS FX without JS. Create custom frontend develop-

ment tools with added subtle automation and CLI.

Internet Mastermind

2014-2015

2004-2018

Software Engineer (frontend)

Malaysia

Implement UI and UX for marketing related applications with Bootstrap UI framework. Frontend and backend UI prototyping (web, app). Custom web design with WordPress.

EDUCATIONS

Shrewsbury College

Visual Art & Design

HK

2008-2009

I also am artist. I gave myself a chance to step into a little bit deeper into the art. Also, I am a perfectionist either in UI or

UX.

Univ. Manchester

Electrical & Electronic Engineering

UK

2002-2005 I was always wanting to be an inventor like robotic, anything since I was a little kid. But, well, they all came true. I just kept

doing it. Never stop.

Chung Ling H. S.

1995-2000

Form 5

Malaysia

Just an ordinary student not very fond of school subjects, beside the computer programming and science classes.

Never a good chance in Art class.

SKILLS

Embedded Development Linux Env.	Software Development Essential for Eng.	
Web Development	Team Player / Leadership	
Material Design	Kanban, Automate	
Machine Learning	Material Design	
NumPy, Sklearn	UI, illustration, FX	